{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": " JSON elements are separated by the ___.",
      "choices": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "label": "line break",
          "value": "line-break"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "label": "semi-colon",
          "value": "semi-colon"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "label": "comma",
          "value": "comma"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "label": "white space",
          "value": "white space"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "comma"
    },
    {
      "question": "A _____ indicates an absent value that may exist but be unknown or that may not exist at all.",
      "choices": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "label": "Empty tuple",
          "value": "empty-tuple"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "label": "New value",
          "value": "new-value"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "label": "Null value",
          "value": "null-value"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "label": "Old value",
          "value": "old-value"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "null-value"
    },
    {
      "question": "JSON stands for ________________",
      "choices": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "label": "Java Standard Output Network",
          "value": "java-standard-output-network"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "label": "JavaScript Object Notation",
          "value": "javaScript-object-notation"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "label": "JavaScript Output Name",
          "value": "javaScript-output-name"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "label": "Java Source Open Network",
          "value": "java-source-open-network"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "javaScript-object-notation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a type in JSON?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "label": "date",
          "value": "date"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "label": "Object",
          "value": "object"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "label": "Array",
          "value": "array"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "label": "string",
          "value": "string"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "date"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are two main structures compose JSON?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "label": "Arrays and Objects",
          "value": "arrays-and-objects"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "label": "Keys and values",
          "value": "keys-and-values"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "label": "Class and Objects",
          "value": "class-and-objects"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "label": "None of above",
          "value": "none-of-above"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "keys-and-values"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following Protocol services uses JSON?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "label": "SMTP",
          "value": "SMTP"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "label": "HTTP",
          "value": "HTTP"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "label": "TCP/IP",
          "value": "TCP/IP"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "label": "Web Protocol",
          "value": "web-protocol"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "HTTP"
    },
    {
      "question": "JSON is derived from the ______ programming language?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "label": "Java",
          "value": "java"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "label": "ECMScript",
          "value": "ECMScript"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "label": "PHP",
          "value": "php"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "label": "JavaScript",
          "value": "javascript"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "javascript"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following JSON feature ensures communication between two applications designed in different programming languages?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "label": "Extensibility",
          "value": "Extensibility"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "label": "Scalability",
          "value": "Scalability"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "label": "Interoperability",
          "value": "Interoperability"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "label": "Reusability",
          "value": "Reusability"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Interoperability"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the MIME type of JSON?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "label": "application/x-json",
          "value": "application/x-json"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "label": "text/json",
          "value": "text/json"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "label": "application/json",
          "value": "application/json"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "label": "application/javascript",
          "value": "application/javascript"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "application/json"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these is supported as a JSON Value type?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "label": "Infiniti",
          "value": "Infiniti"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "label": "Null",
          "value": "Null"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "label": "Undefined",
          "value": "Undefined"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "label": "NaN",
          "value": "NaN"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Null"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the file extension of JSON?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "label": ".jsn",
          "value": ".jsn"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "label": ".js",
          "value": ".js"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "label": ".json",
          "value": ".json"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "label": ".jxn",
          "value": ".jxn"
        }
      ],
      "answer": ".json"
    }
  ]
}
